nrs.com 2013-11-28

# NRS Privacy and Security Policy at NRS.com

I.  The NRS Commitment to Secure Online Shopping:

  * NRS understands your concerns about privacy.  We have both electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard information you give us online.  NRS uses GeoTrust to provide secure online communications by encrypting all data (including your payment information) transmitted to and from the NRSWeb.com website.

---|---|---|---|---  

II. Personal Information that NRS May Collect Online:

  * NRS collects and retains customer names, postal and email addresses, billing information, and phone and fax numbers for our own use.

III.  How NRS Uses Your Personal Information:

  * The collection of customer names, postal and email addresses, billing information, and phone numbers is used for order processing and communication regarding your NRS order. 

  * When you supply NRS with your email address, you may receive periodic mailings of the NRS electronic newsletter.  We use NRS E-News to notify you of special offers, tips, and new gear. If you would rather not receive this inside information, please go to NRS e-News Unsubscribe page and enter your email to manually unsubscribe or give us a call at 1.877.677.4327.

  * When you supply NRS with your postal address, you may receive periodic mailings of the NRS printed catalog. From time to time NRS may share your name with other high-quality companies that we feel may match your adventurous spirit. If you would rather not receive our catalog or  information from other paddlesports companies, please call 877.677.4327, write to NRS at 2009 S. Main St. Moscow, ID 83843, or email [service@nrs.com](mailto:service@nrs.com) and ask to be omitted. 

IV.  " Cookies" and Site Usage Tracking:

  * A "Cookie" is a text file that allows you to retain the contents of your shopping cart while you continue to shop. Cookies also save your personal settings so you don't have to enter them every time you shop at NRSWeb.com. Payment information is not stored in your cookies and the existence of a cookie does not breach your privacy. Cookies save you time by remembering your personalized settings. Cookies are stored as temporary internet files on your computer. In order for somebody to access the information stored in your cookie they would need to hack into your personal computer. The information cannot be accessed through our web server. Cookies are also used by NRS to collect information on what areas of our web site are most popular, allowing us to better organize our site to suit your needs. We do not use personal information provided for any other purpose.

V. Children

  * NRS asks that children do not submit information to us without the consent of a parent or guardian. 

VI.  Access to Personal Information

  * If you would like to update, review, or remove your personal information from the NRS database, please call 877.677.4327, write to NRS at 2009 S. Main Moscow, ID 83843, or email [service@nrs.com](mailto:service@nrs.com) and tell us what you would like us to do.

VII. Google Analytics

  *
